Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Publications Collection, 1887-2005 RL.00741
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Domestic Publications Series (Restricted), 1887-2005 and undated, 32 boxes
  - General Publications, 1887-2005 and undated
    - 1990
      - JWT Media Person's Handbook (Box DG22)
      - Look at 15-Second Commercials in the 90s (Box DG22)
      - Looking Forward to the Next 10 Years (Box DG22)
      - TV Fact Book (Box DG22)
      - What Others Really Think About Account Managers (Box DG22)
    - 1991
      - Advertising in the '90s (Box DG22)
      - Commodore (Box DG22)
      - How to Become an Advertising Man (Box DG22)
      - J. Walter Thompson USA (Box DG22)
      - JWT New Business Handbook (Box DG22)
      - Paradox Papers: Marketing in Modern Times (Box DG22)
      - Presentation to Exxon Company (Box DG22)
      - Technique for Producing Ideas/James Webb Young (Box DG22)
      - Thompson Office Manager's Handbook (Box DG22)
      - TV Fact Book (Box DG22)
      - U.S. Consumer Media (Box DG22)
  - General Publications, Restricted Materials (Closed to non-JWT users), 1992-2005
    - 1992
      - Buying: It's Not an Event, It's a System (Box DG23)
      - Can J. Walter Thompson Make Your Marketing Programs More Effective? (Box DG23)
      - Creative Research in the 1990s (Box DG23)
      - Jaguar: A Love Affair (Box DG23)
      - JWT New Business Checklist for Winners (Box DG23)
      - Looking Up at JWT (Box DG23)
      - Miracle Whip: I Couldn't Make It Without You! Cookbook (Box DG23)
      - Paradox Papers
        - Marketing in Modern Times (Box DG23)
        - Youth in the 90s (Box DG23)
      - Partial Checklist of J. Walter Thompson Domestic Clients for Shopping Purposes (Box DG23)
      - People Buy Brands, Not Products (Box DG23)
      - Professional Development Manual, 2 folders (Box DG24)
      - Some Things We Have Learned About Managing a JWT Office (Box DG24)
      - TV Fact Book (Box DG24)
    - 1993
      - Account Management Performance Evaluation, Tips, Checklist (Box DG24)
      - Eyes on Thompson program
        - Brands: Their Value and Valuation (Box DG24)
        - Commercial Showreel (NTSC) (Box DG24)
        - Developing the Big Match Temperament (Box DG24)
      - JWT Director-in-Charge: Roles and Expectations (Box DG24)
      - JWT Management Leadership Program, Duke University (Box DG24)
      - Partial Checklist of JWT Domestic Clients for Shopping Reference (Box DG24)
    - 1994
      - Buying: It's Not an Event, It's a System (Box DG24)
      - Creative Research in the 1990s (Box DG24)
      - Employee Benefits Booklet (Box DG24)
      - J. Walter Merchandise Catalog (Box DG24)
      - J. Walter Source (Box DG24)
      - Power of the Old, Shock of the New (Box DG24)
      - Technique for Producing Ideas/James Webb Young (Box DG24)
      - Worldwide White Pea Awards (Box DG25)
    - 1995
      - Handbook (Box DG25)
      - Pamphlet Collection (Box DG25)
      - Paradox Papers: Marketing in Modern Times (Box DG25)
      - People Buy Brands, Not Products (Box DG25)
      - TV Fact Book (Box DG25)
    - 1996
      - It's a World, 3 folders (Box DG25)
      - JWT Cuisine: A Collection of Recipes from Employees and Friends of JWT Worldwide (Box DG25)
      - Net-Working: A Research Study on Employment and the Internet (Box DG25)
      - Paradox Papers: Marketing in Modern Times (Box DG25)
      - Partial Checklist of JWT Domestic Clients for Shopping Reference (Box DG25)
      - Transformation (Box DG25)
    - 1997
      - 1996 J. Walter Thompson Yearbook (Box DG25)
      - Advertising and Marketing Bibliography (Box DG25)
      - Brand Management: A Guide to a Few Misconceptions (Box DG25)
      - Integrated Marketing Communications: A Return to Basics (Box DG26)
      - Media Research Sources (Box DG26)
      - Memorandum and Introductory Package Regarding JWT's Transformation (Box DG26)
      - New Visual Identity (Box DG26)
      - Paradox Papers: Marketing in Modern Times (Box DG26)
      - Thompson Total Branding (4 booklets) (Box DG26)
      - U.S. Clients (Box DG26)
    - 1998
      - Business of Imagination: The Art of Creating Convictions (Box DG26)
      - Employee Handbook (Box DG26)
      - Fish (Box DG26)
      - JWT Guide to Research (Box DG26)
      - Thompson Total Branding Guidebook (Box DG26)
    - 1999
      - New Image Package (Box DG26)
      - Our Best Total Branding (Box DG26)
      - Year in View (Box DG26)
    - circa 1990s
      - Buying: It's Not an Event, It's a System (Box DG26)
      - J. Walter Merchandise Catalog (Box DG26)
      - J. Walter Thompson Company (Box DG27)
      - J. Walter Thompson Identity Guidelines (Box DG27)
      - Managing the Agency (Box DG27)
      - Reflections on an Agency/Peter Yeo (Box DG27)
      - Selling The Most Effective, Distinctive Advertising in the Marketplace (Box DG27)
      - Some Things We Have Learned About Managing a JWT Office (Box DG27)
      - Thompson Red Book on Advertising (Box DG27)
      - Thompson Way Handbook (Box DG27)
    - 2000
      - New Business Services (Box DG27)
      - Year in View (Box DG27)
    - 2001
      - Some Things We Have Learned About Building Client Relationships (Box DG27)
    - 2002
      - [ Passion: North America (Bound volume of advertisements, removed to Oversize Materials, box OV2)] (Box DG27)
      - Some Things We Have Learned About Building Client Relationships (Box DG27)
      - What I Had To Do (Box DG27)
    - 2003
      - [ Passion: North America (Bound volume of advertisements, removed to Oversize Materials, box OV2)] (Box DG27)
    - 2004
      - J. Walter Thompson (Box DG27)
      - Open Letter to Our Cohorts at JWT (Box DG27)
    - 2005
      - [ Hold My Skateboard While I Kiss Your Girlfriend (Bound volume of advertisements, removed to Oversize Materials, box OV2)] (Box DG27)
  - Interurbia, 1957-1960
    - 1957-1960, 8 folders (Box DG28)
  - Individual Offices Publications, 1909-2003 and undated
    Arranged alphabetically by office and publication title.
    - Atlanta
      - CIBA-GEIGY Agricultural Division, 1984 (Box DO1)
      - Florida Department of Citrus, 1982 (Box DO1)
      - JWT Coloring Book, 1974 (Box DO1)
    - Chicago
      - Consumer in Crisis: the New American Market, 1974 (Box DO1)
      - Couponing: A Capsule Look, 1970 (Box DO1)
      - Engine Room, undated (Box DO1)
      - General Subject Headings Used in the JWT-Chicago Library, 1965 (Box DO1)
      - Generation Gap: A Problem of Communication, 1970 (Box DO1)
      - How to Pick an Advertising Agency, undated (Box DO1)
      - How to Promote Your Restaurant, 1965 (Box DO1)
      - How to Put a Spec Book Together, undated (Box DO1)
      - J. Walter Thompson Company, 1986 (Box DO1)
      - J. Walter Who?, 1988 (Box DO1)
      - JWT Chicago, 1967 (Box DO1)
      - [ JWT Employee Handbook, 1993 (Removed to Individual Offices, Restricted Materials, box DO4)] (Box DO1)
      - JWT Office, John Hancock Center, circa 1969 (Box DO1)
      - Market Study for the Professional Nutritionist, 1975 (Box DO1)
      - Pocket Guide to Media Terms and Media Math, 1979 (Box DO1)
      - Preparedness for Peace, 1916 (Box DO1)
      - Proposal: Corporate Communications/Jack Hilton, 1971 (Box DO1)
      - Review and Summary of the Published Literature on Eating Out, 1964 (Box DO1)
      - Role of Account Management at JWT Chicago, 1986 (Box DO1)
      - Standards for Report Typing
        - Typing and Preparation of Research Reports and Correspondence, 1963 (Box DO1)
        - Writing, Editing and General Construction, 1963 (Box DO2)
      - Tele-Communications, undated (Box DO2)
      - Yearbook, 1997, 1998, 2 folders (Box DO2)
    - Cleveland
      - Few More Chapters, circa 1909 (Box DO2)
    - Detroit
      - Advertising in a Land of Less: circa 1980, 1975 (Box DO2)
      - [ Guide to Central America, 1996 (Removed to Individual Offices, Restricted Materials, box DO4)], 2 folders (Box DO2)
      - JWT Detroit, 1975 (Box DO2)
      - JWT Detroit Public Relations, circa 1987 (Box DO2)
      - Merchandise Catalog, 1997 (Box DO2)
      - Performance Group, circa 1984 (Box DO2)
      - [ Rhapsody in Red II, 1995 (Removed to Individual Offices, Restricted Materials, box DO4)] (Box DO2)
      - Six Things Most Ad Agencies Would Never Say to a Client, circa 1986 (Box DO2)
      - We've Made Our Move in Detroit, undated (Box DO2)
    - Los Angeles
      - [ Cable/Satellite Industry Blue Book, 1998 (Removed to Individual Offices, Restricted Materials, box DO4)], 2 folders (Box DO2)
    - New York
      - Breads of Many Lands, 1957 (Box DO2)
      - Brief Profile of JWT New York, undated (Box DO2)
      - Brief Profile of the J. Walter Thompson Company, 1981 (Box DO2)
      - Comparison of Type Faces, circa 1957 (Box DO2)
      - Conquest Europe, 1988 (Box DO2)
      - Electronic Production Services, undated (Box DO2)
      - G-8, 1967 (Box DO2)
      - Information Center, 1983 (Box DO2)
      - J. Walter Thompson New York, 1982 (Box DO2)
      - Lippold Sculpture Construction, 1961 (Box DO2)
      - Media Merchandising Services, 1947 (Box DO2)
      - Mexican Mystique, 1957 (Box DO2)
      - [ New York Office Guidebook, circa 2003 (Removed to Individual Offices, Restricted Materials, box DO4)] (Box DO2)
      - Pet Food Market, 1974 (Box DO2)
      - Professional Forum, 1971 (Box DO2)
      - Questions and Answers in Planning Advertising, undated (Box DO2)
      - T-Plan, undated (Box DO2)
      - Why Work for a Living? 1985 (Box DO2)
    - San Francisco
      - [ Be Big, 1994 (Removed to Individual Offices, Restricted Materials, box DO4)] (Box DO3)
      - [ Creative Library, 1997 (Removed to Individual Offices, Restricted Materials, box DO4)], 2 folders (Box DO3)
      - Guide to Selective Selling and Merchandising in 143 U.S. Cities, 1941 (Box DO3)
      - J. Walter Thompson San Francisco, 1986 (Box DO3)
      - [ JWT West Employee Training Handbook, 1994 (Removed to Individual Offices, Restricted Materials, box DO4)] (Box DO3)
      - México, undated (Box DO3)
      - [ Power of the Old, Shock of the New, 1994 (Removed to Individual Offices, Restricted Materials, box DO4)] (Box DO3)
      - Price Guarantees by Manufacturers with Sales Contracts, 1936 (Box DO3)
    - Washington, D.C.
      - JWT Washington: What It Is, What It Does, 1974 (Box DO3)
  - Individual Offices, Restricted Materials (Closed to non-JWT users), 1993-2003
    - Chicago (Box DO4)
      - JWT Employee Handbook, 1993 (Box DO4)
    - Detroit
      - Guide to Central America, 1996, 2 folders (Box DO4)
      - Michigan Opera Theatre commemorative issue, 1998 (Box DO4)
      - Rhapsody in Red, 1994 (Box DO4)
      - Rhapsody in Red II, 1995 (Box DO4)
    - Los Angeles
      - Cable Satellite Industry Blue Book, 1998, 2 folders (Box DO4)
    - New York
      - New York Office Guidebook, circa 2003 (Box DO4)
    - San Francisco
      - Be Big, 1994 (Box DO4)
      - Creative Library, 1997, 2 folders (Box DO4)
      - JWT West Employee Training Handbook, 1994 (Box DO4)
      - Power of the Old, Shock of the New, 1994 (Box DO4)
- International Publications Series (Restricted), 1914-2003 and undated, 22 boxes
  Organized into three categories--London Office Publications, London/Manchester Office Publications, and Other Offices Publications. London publications are arranged chronologically; other subseries are arranged alphabetically by office name and title.
  - London Office Publications, 1920-2003 and undated
    Arranged chronologically and alphabetically therein.
    - 1920 (Box IL1)
      - Resumption of Overseas Buying (Box IL1)
    - 1931
      - Market Analysis of the 1931 Population Statistics for Great Britain and Ireland (Box IL1)
    - 1934
      - How to Measure the Value of Advertising (Box IL1)
    - 1937
      - Opportunities for American Manufacturers in Britain Today (Box IL1)
    - 1946
      - Advertising in Small Spaces (Box IL1)
    - 1949
      - What is Marketing? (Box IL1)
    - 1950
      - Self Service in Great Britain (Box IL1)
    - 1954
      - Career in Advertising (Box IL1)
    - 1955
      - International Organization of the J. Walter Thompson Company Ltd. (Box IL1)
    - 1956
      - Career in Advertising (Box IL1)
    - 1959
      - Development of Independent Television (Box IL1)
    - 1961
      - European View of the Common Market (Box IL1)
      - Television Attention Research (Box IL1)
    - 1962
      - Times (Box IL1)
    - 1963
      - Social Change in Britain by 1984 (Box IL1)
      - World-Wide Opportunities for Better Living Standards (Box IL1)
    - 1964
      - Challenges and Problems for International Adversiting (Box IL1)
      - Changing Face of Super Market Shopping (Box IL1)
      - Client/Agency Relationship (Box IL1)
      - Decade of Change (Box IL1)
      - Forecasting the Demand for Consumer Durables (Box IL1)
      - How Many Nations? (Box IL2)
      - Mirror for a Lady (Box IL2)
      - Pin-Pointing the Affluent Household (Box IL2)
      - Report on Advertising Agencies in the Far East (Box IL2)
      - T-Plan (Box IL2)
      - Will Advertising Need Smaller Targets and Better Gun-Sights? (Box IL2)
    - 1965
      - Company Advertising/London (Box IL2)
      - JWT 1965 (Box IL2)
      - One World of J. Walter Thompson Company: A Guide to 37 International Offices in 24 Countries (Box IL2)
      - Sales Curves of New Products (Box IL2)
      - Validity of Test Marketing (Box IL2)
      - What Puts the Prices Up? (Box IL2)
    - 1966
      - Colour Television- A Report (Box IL2)
      - Freeze-Drying Process (Box IL2)
      - International Advertising Agency (Box IL2)
      - JWT London: 1926-1966 (Box IL2)
      - Three Myths About Our Export Trade (Box IL2)
      - West Germany- A Lost Opportunity? (Box IL2)
    - 1967
      - [ 40 Berkeley Square (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV3)] (Box IL2)
      - Advertising--Is This The Sort of Work An Honest Man Can Take Pride In? (Box IL2)
      - Advertising and Sales Promotion Expenditure (Box IL2)
      - At The Receiving End (Box IL2)
      - Can Research Evaluate the Creative Content of Advertising? (Box IL2)
      - How Useful is Proposition Testing? (Box IL2)
      - JWT Decimal Money Experiment (Box IL2)
      - New Housewife, 2 folders (Box IL2)
      - Operational Research and Marketing (Box IL2)
      - Report on Private Label in U.S. Food Retailing (Box IL2)
      - What Do We Know About How Advertising Works? (Box IL2)
    - 1968
      - Grocery Marketing: The Next Five Years (Box IL2)
      - International Advertising- The Wheel Is Turning Full Circle (Box IL2)
      - Market Research and the Retailer (Box IL2)
      - Pharmaceutical Advertising and Marketing (Box IL2)
    - 1969
      - JWT In Britain (Box IL2)
      - Techniques in Market Forecasting (Box IL2)
      - What Say The Augurers? (Box IL2)
    - 1970 (Box IL3)
      - Advertising Expenditures in Western Europe 1960-70 (Box IL3)
      - Advertising Management (Box IL3)
      - Gravity of Marketing (Box IL3)
      - JWT In Britain (Box IL3)
      - JWT London: Dates and Data (Box IL3)
      - Private Label Reviewed (Box IL3)
      - Retailing in the Seventies (Box IL3)
    - 1971
      - JWT Handbook (Box IL3)
      - Market Research on a European Basis (Box IL3)
      - Relationship Between Purchasing Patterns and Advertising Exposure (Box IL3)
      - What is a Brand? (Box IL3)
    - 1972
      - Advertising: An Annotated Bibliography (Box IL3)
      - Ethiopian Endeavor (Box IL3)
      - JWT London: The Consumer Has A Mind As Well As A Stomach (Box IL3)
      - Presentation Didn't Go Quite As We Expected... (Box IL3)
      - Sources of Information on European Countries (Box IL3)
      - Tomorrow's Consumer (Box IL3)
      - Tomorrow's Food (Box IL3)
    - 1973
      - Almost Every Other Company You Consider Joining Uses Someone Like Us (Box IL3)
      - Do You Know Your Way Around Europe? (Box IL3)
      - Great Outdoors (Box IL3)
      - How Much Do T.V. Commercials Cost To Make? (Box IL3)
      - JWT In Britain (Box IL4)
      - New Wavelength (Box IL4)
      - Some Observations On Forecasting and Planning (Box IL4)
      - Television In Europe (Box IL4)
    - 1973-1974
      - Guiness (Box IL4)
    - 1974
      - How Advertising Works (Box IL4)
      - Information that Never Got into the Files (Box IL4)
      - JWT In Britain (Box IL4)
      - JWT In Europe (Box IL4)
      - Media Digest- Europe (Box IL4)
      - Project Norway (Box IL4)
      - Read All About It! (Box IL4)
    - 1974-1975
      - Guiness Advertising (Box IL4)
    - 1975
      - Advertising Expenditures in Western Europe 1960-1974 (Box IL4)
      - Case for Advertising (Box IL4)
      - Contact Advertising Limited (Box IL4)
      - JWT In Britain (Box IL4)
      - Media Digest- Europe (Box IL5)
      - Practical Progress From A Theory of Adverstiments (Box IL5)
      - Trends and Retail Sales 1966-1975 (Box IL5)
      - Women's Use of Media (Box IL5)
    - 1975-1976
      - People's Use of Media (Box IL5)
    - 1976
      - Case for Advertising (Box IL5)
      - Consumer Change and Conflict (Box IL5)
      - Consumer Change in the Mid 70's (Box IL5)
      - JWT In Britain (Box IL5)
      - JWT In London, in Europe and Around the World (Box IL5)
      - JWT Information Services- Europe (Box IL5)
      - Market Sizes (Box IL5)
    - 1977
      - Advertising Expenditures: International Comparisons 1960-1975 (Box IL5)
      - Guide To JWT In Europe (Box IL5)
      - History of Berkeley Square (Box IL5)
      - JWT In Britain (Box IL5)
      - Media Digest- Europe (Box IL5)
    - 1978 (Box IL6)
      - Crisis in Branding (Box IL6)
      - James Walter Thompson Advertising Agent (Box IL6)
      - JWT 1978 (Box IL6)
      - Notice to All Employees (Box IL6)
      - Research Into Attitudes to Advertising (Box IL6)
      - Thompson Redbook (Box IL6)
    - 1979
      - Information Services
        - Advertising Business 2nd Quarter 1979 (Box IL6)
        - Guide to Resources (Box IL6)
        - Multinational Advertising Bibliography (Box IL6)
        - Representatives' Basic Reading List (Box IL6)
    - 1979-1980
      - Guinness Advertising (Box IL6)
    - 1980
      - Best Sellers (Box IL6)
      - Effective Advertising (Box IL6)
      - JWT 80 London (Box IL6)
      - JWT 80 Manchester (Box IL6)
    - 1980-1981
      - Guinness Advertising (Box IL6)
    - 1981
      - Home Video (Box IL6)
      - JWT 1981: A Review of the Year's Advertising (Box IL6)
      - Winner's Manual... (Box IL6)
    - 1982 (Box IL7)
      - Viewdata (Box IL7)
    - 1983
      - List of Accounts (Box IL7)
      - New Business Brochures (Box IL7)
      - Television Today--Television Tomorrow (Box IL7)
    - 1984
      - April 1984 (Box IL7)
      - Copy Test (Box IL7)
      - Developing New Brands (Box IL7)
      - Effective Advertising: 4 Case Studies (Box IL7)
      - Information Services: Lifestyle Trends (Box IL7)
      - JWT 1984 (Box IL7)
      - List of Accounts (Box IL7)
    - 1984-1991
      - Graduate Recruitment Seminar, 7 folders (Box IL7)
    - 1985
      - Bush House, Berlin and Berkeley Square (Box IL7)
      - Why Work for a Living? (Box IL7)
    - 1985-1986
      - 1985/1986 (Box IL7)
    - 1986
      - Floating Thames (Box IL7)
      - Issue (Box IL7)
    - 1987
      - 50th Anniversary Kit Kat (Box IL7)
      - 86-87 Face to Face with JWT (Box IL7)
      - Acorn to Zapping (Box IL7)
      - I Hear What You Say... (Box IL7)
    - 1988
      - King Papers (Box IL7)
    - 1989
      - Adspend Today, Adspent Tomorrow (Box IL7)
      - JWT Effective Advertising Programme (Box IL7)
    - 1989-1990
      - J. Walter Thompson Professional Development Programme (Box IL7)
    - 1990
      - [ JWT Rises to the Challenge of Europe (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV3)] (Box IL7)
      - Mysteries of Time and Space (Box IL7)
    - 1991
      - Handbook of Effective Advertising (Box IL7)
  - London Office, Restricted Materials (Closed to non-JWT users), 1992-2003 and undated
    - 1992 (Box IL8)
      - Dear Personalized (Box IL8)
      - Great Call Reports (Box IL8)
      - J. Walter Thompson Direct (Box IL8)
    - 1993
      - Fourth Stage Consumer (Box IL8)
    - 1995
      - Cold Hard Facts (Box IL8)
    - 1996
      - Advanced Media Solutions (Box IL8)
      - Fifty in 40 (Box IL8)
    - 1999
      - Computer Skills Programme: Introduction to Notes Mail (Box IL8)
      - Focus: The Lab (Box IL9)
      - Visualize: Sharing Resources (Box IL9)
      - Visualize: The Internet (Box IL9)
    - 1990s, 2002
      - Great Media Ideas (Box IL9)
    - 2001
      - [ Knightsbridge Green Blueprint (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV3)] (Box IL9)
    - 2003
      - Liberation (Box IL9)
    - Undated
      - Jump Start Cards (Box IL9)
      - JWT Graduate Recruitment (Box IL9)
      - JWT Knowledge Centre (Box IL9)
      - Roadmap of Greenland (Box IL9)
  - London/Manchester Office Publications, 1984-1991
    - 1984 (Box IL10)
      - Media Market in 1988 (Box IL10)
    - 1990
      - Manchester (Box IL10)
    - 1991
      - Problem (Box IL10)
  - Other Offices Publications, 1914-2003 and undated
    - Argentina
      - De Medio à Medio, 1984 (Box IO1)
      - El Mercado Norteamericano Para Articulos de Ultramar, 1950 (Box IO1)
      - En La Argentina, 1969 (Box IO1)
      - Encuestas Exploratorias de Grupo, 1980s (Box IO1)
      - J. Walter Thompson Argentina SRI, circa 1964 (Box IO1)
      - [ Manual Operativa para Cuentas, 1994 (Removed to Other Offices Publications, Restricted Materials, box IO12)], 2 folders (Box IO1)
      - Nombreme, circa 1979 (Box IO1)
      - Pamphlets, circa 1991 (Box IO1)
      - This Is Argentina, 1961 (Box IO1)
      - [ Thompson Way, 1991: Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV4] (Box IO1)
    - Asia Pacific
      - [ Don't Blink: The Third Beat Passion, 2002 (Bound volume of advertisements, removed to Oversize Materials, box OV4)] (Box IO1)
    - Australia
      - Australian Underview, circa 1980 (Box IO1)
      - Definition and Explanation of Terms Used In Advertising, 1964 (Box IO1)
      - [ Dreaming, 1993 (Removed to Other Offices Publications, Restricted Materials, box IO12)] (Box IO1)
      - Introduction to J. Walter Thompson, 1984 (Box IO1)
      - J. Walter Thompson, undated (Box IO1)
      - [ J. Walter Thompson Company Limited, 1983 (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV4)] (Box IO1)
      - J.W.T. Account Team: Responsibilities and Procedures, 1964 (Box IO1)
      - New JWT, undated (Box IO1)
      - Research Department Role and Organization, 1964 (Box IO1)
      - Research Development Procedures, 1964 (Box IO1)
      - Selected Articles on Setting Adversiting Goals and Measuring Results, 1964 (Box IO2)
      - Switchback to Confidence, 1977 (Box IO2)
      - Unified International Practices, 1964 (Box IO2)
      - Welcome to JWT--Sue Dean, undated (Box IO2)
    - Austria
      - Vienna Presents, 1977 (Box IO2)
    - Belgium
      - Comment Vendre, 1933, 1937, 2 folders (Box IO2)
      - Euroscope, 1974 (Box IO2)
      - Government Sponsored Advertising in Europe Today, 1974 (Box IO2)
      - J. Walter Thompson, 1984 (Box IO2)
      - [ J. Walter Thompson, 1984 (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV4)] (Box IO2)
      - Lettre Ouverte, 1935 (Box IO2)
      - L'etude du Marché, 1957 (Box IO2)
      - Management Philosophy, 1973 (Box IO2)
      - Marketing Research, 1957 (Box IO2)
      - New Premises for JWT Brussels, 1973 (Box IO2)
      - Pan-European Communication, 1973 (Box IO2)
      - Photographic Essay, 1970 (Box IO2)
      - Pierre Caille, 1967 (Box IO2)
      - Publicité, 1952 (Box IO2)
    - Brazil
      - Abra as Asas, 1990 (Box IO2)
      - [ Brasil, 1987: REmoved to Oversize Materials, box OV4] (Box IO2)
      - Guideline for Crisis Situations, 1983 (Box IO2)
      - Iniciativa Privada na Construção da sociedade, 1966 (Box IO2)